We're going to take a little break from the lesson to become a bit more familiar
我们先把课程放一下 来熟悉一下
with Alteryx.
Alteryx 软件
Since we'll be using Alteryx for a good part of this course to demonstrate how
因为本课程主要使用 Alteryx 软件来展示
to build an analytic data set, let's explore some basic capabilities so
如何构建一个数据分析集 我们将学习一些基本功能
that when you go to use it, you're a little more comfortable with the tool.
以便于你以后使用的时候更得心应手
We're first going to get familiar with how to bring data into Alteryx.
我们先学习一下怎么向 Alteryx 中导入数据
To start, I'm going to simply click on the Input Data tool, and
首先 点击一下 Input Data 工具
drop it onto the canvas.
然后将其拖到画板上
Next I'll click over to the Configuration window, and
然后 点击一下 Configuration 框
then to the drop-down arrow, and choose File Browse.
点击下拉箭头 选择 File Browse
From here you can see the various file types supported by the Alteryx software.
这里可以看到 Alteryx 软件支持的所有文件类型
Next I'm going to navigate to where the sample data is located for
接下来 找到位于 Alteryx 文件夹中的 sample data 文件夹
Alteryx, choose a file, click on Open, and
选择文件夹 点击打开
then choose the sheet that says Output$ and then OK.
选择名字为 Output$ 的表格 点击 OK
We can see the data on the left in the preview window, and
我们就可以在左侧预览窗口看到数据了
the file is now opened in Alteryx.
现在文件就在 Alteryx 被打开了
Now that we know how to open a file in Alterxy, let's look at a few additional
现在我们知道了怎么在 Alteryx 中打开文件 我们来学习一下
functionalities that will allow us to explore the data file further.
研究数据文件需要的其他功能
Let's practice building a work flow in Alteryx.
我们来练习下在 Alteryx 中建立一个 work flow
Let's say your boss asks you to tell her how many customers are in the Denver
例如说你老板想知道公司有多少客户
market.
来自 Denver 市场
As a start, it'd be interesting to know how many records total are in the file.
首先 我们想知道文件中有多少条记录
This can be done really easily by simply running the work flow.
这只要运行一下 work flow 00:01:19,740 --&gt; 00:01:22,350 我们可以通过点击 play 按钮 或者
hitting Ctrl+R on the keyboard.
使用快捷键 Ctrl+R
Once the workflow is run, we can navigate to the Results window,
一旦 workflow 开始运行 找到 Results 窗口 00:01:28,640 --&gt; 00:01:36,010. 点击 Messages 图标 就可以看到文件有2669条记录
By clicking on the Output icon, we can see the data and the fields in the file.
点击一下 Output 图标 我们可以看到文件中的数据和字段
But our boss is only interested in analyzing the customers
但是老板只想分析客户中
who are in Denver.
Denver 客户
We can use the Filter tool to isolate these customers out of the larger data
我们可以 Filter 工具从大的数据集中分离出这些
set.
客户数据
We pull the Filter tool onto the canvas and
我们把 Filter 工具拖到面板上
select the City field in the Basic Filter.
在 Basic Filter 中选择 City 字段
In the box to the right of equals, we enter Denver.
在 equals 右边的框中输入 Denver
The Filter tool has two outputs, a T, or true, side and an F, or false, side.
Filter 工具有两个输出 T 真的一侧  和 F 假的一侧
The true side outputs the records where the expression evaluated to true.
真的一侧输出的是表达式为真的记录
So these are the records where the city is Denver.
也就是那些 City 字段为 Denver 的记录
There are 1166 records in that list.
这个列表中有1166条记录
If you click on the false side, you can see the rest of the records for
如果你点击 F 一侧 你就会看到除此之外的
the other cities.
其他城市的记录